

ABOUT

I'm Frontend Developer with more than 2 years of experience specializing in software design and development. I used to work at TMA and AEGONA in a professional environment. I can optimize the software for processing speed to make the user experience better

EDUCATION

HUFLIT (2018 - 2022)

Major: Information Technology Bachelor Degree: Very good

GPA: 8.15



LANGUAGES

English 530 Toeic

Communication intermediate

NGUYỄN KIM TIỀN

MIDDLE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

076 355 7366

Go Vap, TPHCM

☑ tienkim9920@gmail.com

https://tienkim.netlify.app



EXPERIENCE



TMA SOLUTIONS

Time: 2021 - 2022

Fresher Frontend Developer



AEGONA LTD

Time: 2022 - 2023

Junior Frontend Developer



EXPERIENCE SKILLS

?

RESTful API, Analysis Software, Design Pattern, Organization, Lead Team, Design Software



GENERAL SKILLS

9---

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Design, Flutter, NodeJS, Github, Gitlab, Azure Devops.